Max Boonji	IIIUaSUP in LinkedIn ★ Portfolio 👩 GitH	Hub 💆 Kaggle 📞 818-42	8-0901
Skills			
• Languages: Python, SQL, R. Git, Matlab	<ul> <li>Tools: Tableau, Power BI,</li> <li>Docker, Excel, Jupyter</li> <li>Notebook</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Modeling: Regression, Classification, Neural Networks, PCA</li> </ul>	• Statistics: Hypothesis Testing, A/B Testing, Multivariate Analysis
Certificates			
Google Advanced Data Analytics     IBM Data Science		Data Science in Healthcare	
Projects			
09/2023 – present	<ul> <li>Data Market Analysis: Industry &amp; Experience Decoder for Datanerd App</li> <li>Developing a robust model for the Datanerd app that discerns industry categorization and experience levels by processing scraped data sourced from job postings.</li> </ul>		
09/2023 – present	<ul> <li>Deep Dive Analysis on Climate Change and Sriracha Supply</li> <li>Researching climate patterns to examine their effects on the agricultural sector and the cascading influence on the economic supply chain.</li> </ul>		
07/2023 - 08/2023	<ul> <li>Predicting Employee Retention □</li> <li>• Built an employee attrition model (XGBoost - 98% accuracy and precision) that identified 5 key factors for improving employee tenure, leading to a possible 20% increase in project management and employee satisfaction.</li> <li>• Conducted data cleaning, processing, and analysis over a 5-year employee dataset to predict employee retainment and visualized insights through Pandas and Seaborn.</li> </ul>		
04/2023 - 05/2023	<ul> <li>Heart Disease Predictor ☑</li> <li>Developed an ensemble of machine learning models (kNN, NN, XGBoost, DT, SVM) to classify heart disease presence. Employed cross-validation and GridSearchCV for optimization, resulting in a neural network with a 100% accuracy.</li> <li>Performed exploratory data analysis on ~900 patient samples through NumPy, Pandas, and Matplotlib to identify patterns, handle missing/categorical data, and standardize variables.</li> </ul>		
Relevant Experience			
11/2021 – 11/2022 Beverly Hills, USA	<ul> <li>Manager, Beverly Hills Arthritis Associates</li> <li>Automated data analysis of accounting ledger and identified nearly \$100,000 in unpaid accounts.</li> <li>Provided leadership to a team of administrative staff, optimizing patient record coordination, while managing over 120 med-legal cases, data documentation in Epic EHR, and phlebotomy duties.</li> </ul>		
07/2019 - 01/2021 Thousand Oaks, USA	Associate Scientist, Amgen  • Prototyped an end-to-end system that seamlessly automates Amgen's workflow. This encompassed precise data capture, rigorous analysis, and comprehensive reporting for diverse projects, culminating in a		

- Prototyped an end-to-end system that seamlessly automates Amgen's workflow. This encompassed precise data capture, rigorous analysis, and comprehensive reporting for diverse projects, culminating in a company-wide presentation and subsequent leadership role for ongoing development.
- Led multiple method development efforts that progressed 9 drugs towards FDA-approval and market release.

## Education

09/2014 – 06/2018 La Jolla, US Bachelor of Science, University of California San Diego

Cognitive Science with a Specialization in Machine Learning and Neural Computation

09/2014 - 06/2018 La Jolla, US Bachelor of Science, University of California San Diego

Biochemistry and Cell Biology

## **Publications**

## Individual Alpha Frequency Determines the Impact of Bottom-Up Drive on Visual Processing

Stephanie Nelli, Aayushi Malpani, **Max Boonjindasup**, John T Serences, Individual Alpha Frequency Determines the Impact of Bottom-Up Drive on Visual Processing, Cerebral Cortex Communications, Volume 2, Issue 2, 2021, tgab032, https://doi.org/10.1093/texcom/tgab032

## Alpha entrainment of posterior visual cortex impacts visual detection 🛭

Stephanie Nelli, **Max Boonjindasup**, Aayushi Malpani, John Serences; Alpha entrainment of posterior visual cortex impacts visual detection. Journal of Vision 2017;17(10):976.